<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FL4Data-Mining@KDD2023</title>
    <link>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FL4Data-Mining@KDD2023</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://fl4data-mining.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>1. Definitions We collect certain identifying personal data when you sign up to our Service such as your name, email address, PayPal address (if different from email address), and telephone number. The personal data we collect from you is disclosed only in accordance with our Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy.Conclude collects Slack account and access information from Users for the purposes of connecting to the Slack API and to authenticate access to information on the Conclude website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepted Papers</title>
      <link>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/papers/</guid>
      <description>Oral  🏆 Best Student Paper Award: Is Normalization Indispensable for Multi-domain Federated Learning?. Weiming Zhuang, Lingjuan Lyu 🏆 Best Industry Paper Award: Distributed Personalized Empirical Risk Minimization. Yuyang Deng, Mohammad Mahdi Kamani, Pouria Mahdavinia, Mehrdad Mahdavi  Poster  Once-for-All Federated Learning: Learning From and Deploying to Heterogeneous Clients. Kamala Varma, Enmao Diao, Tanya Roosta, Jie Ding, Tao Zhang SparseVFL: Communication-Efficient Vertical Federated Learning Based on Sparsification of Embeddings and Gradients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Submissions</title>
      <link>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/calls/</guid>
      <description>Workshop Scope By hosting this workshop at SIGKDD, we hope to promote the development of federated learning as a scientific field and encourage data mining researchers and practitioners to collaborate on this important research topic. We envision the workshop will bring in an overall advancement of FL and broaden its impact in the data mining research and industrial community, while FL has become an increasingly important tool for data mining in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynotes</title>
      <link>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/speakers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizers</title>
      <link>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/organizers/</guid>
      <description>Workshop Committees  Junyuan Hong, Michigan State University  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedules</title>
      <link>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/schedules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fl4data-mining.github.io/schedules/</guid>
      <description>Workshop Schedule (Pacific Timezone, Room 102B)  Time Event Title Event --   8:00 am - 8:05 am  Opening Ceremony    8:05 am - 8:50 am  Keynote Talk 1: Jian Pei Data Valuation in Federated Learning   8:50 am - 9:35 am  Keynote Talk 2: Salman Avestimehr FedLLM: Federated Training of Large Language Models on Private, Sensitive, and Siloed Data  [Slides]   9:35 am - 10:00 am  Coffee Break    10:00 am - 10:45 am  Keynote Talk 3: Yiran Chen Revolutionizing Federated Learning: A Leap in Efficiency, Robustness, and Performance   10:45 am - 11:30 am  Keynote Talk 4: Aidong Zhang Multi-party Learning in Federated Environments   11:30 am - 12:00 pm  Poster Presentation    12:00 pm - 1:00 pm  Lunch Break    1:00 pm - 1:15 pm  Oral Presentation 1 Distributed Personalized Empirical Risk Minimization   1:15 pm - 1:30 pm  Oral Presentation 2 Is Normalization Indispensable for Multi-domain Federated Learning?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
